(Amy:)Catchy.
(Raj:)I'm gonna
check the temp on the tub.
(Bernadette:)Don't make it too hot.
Sorry, but "too hot"
(Howard:)is the only temperature
I come in.
(Bernadette:)Look at that...
(Bernadette:)you shaved it all.
(Sheldon:)You're welcome.
(Howard:)Um, question...
this is my first hot tub...
(Howard:)is it supposed to come with
a rat flopping around in it?
(Bernadette:)Ew, really? Get it out.
(Howard:)How?
Uh...
(Bernadette:)wish we had a skimmer.
(Howard:)Uh, you turn off the jets,
(Howard:)I'll get a strainer
from the kitchen.
(Bernadette:)I don't know how
to turn off the jets.
(Howard:)Good, I don't know
where we keep the strainer.
(Leonard:)Excuse me.
(Leonard:)Uh, bad news.
The maître d' said
it's gonna be at least an hour.
(Penny:)An hour? What? That's crazy.
We have a reservation.